My hostel room looks more like an
office cabin than a room and I have been living in it for almost one and a half
years.  So if I
start telling its demerits then it will be evening but it is okay, everything has its due.
Now
accepting this, I finally decided to give myself
a great makeover.  Ok.  So let's first
start with Almirah.  I do
n't know much about painting but I can't live without showing off my art.
So I
decided to paint Shinchan on one side of
it.  Not Gonna Live.  It is not a masterpiece but it is not
bad either.  And on the front side
I have made something like this teddy bear.
Now I feel cute.  If I don't feel cute
after all the hard work I have put in in this heat, then
who will?  And
subscribe for part two because there's
more humiliation of the room to come.